MISAEL VILLAVERDE

misaelvilla10@gmail.com \diamond potifar.dev

OBJECTIVE

Software developer seeking for great projects to contribute on.

SKILLS

Technical Skills.

Most proficient with Go and TypeScript, but I'm pretty much language agnostic.

Have also worked with C# and Python, played with Rust and OCaml, and finished courses on C++ and Java.

Backend: Golang, Node.js, CapRover, Supabase, Firebase and more.

Databases: Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Redis.

Frontend: SwiftUI on iOS/macOS and Next.js, Alpine.js on the web (also full SSR with HTMX and Go).

Cloud experience: Google Cloud Platform, Azure, and Cloudflare.

Languages. Spanish: Native, English: Professional proficiency.

EXPERIENCE

Rumis App 2024 - today

Founder and Software Engineer

Panamá, Panamá

• The way to create groups of roomies and find rooms, using AI

Omniscape XR Nov 2021 - today

FullStack Software Developer (Main backend)

North Carolina, United States (remote)

- Main Dev at the team responsible for OmniscapeXR web platforms (VR, AR).
- Worked with 3D on the web technologies such as deck.gl and h3.js.
- Built the 3D Marketplace for items compatible with the OmniscapeXR Platforms and the Virtual Real Estate Platforms.
- Built the Core Services API in golang to handle authenticated requests and CRUD + Ad Hoc operations for all 3 Apps (desktop, mobile and web).

HypernovaLabs

Jun 2021 - Nov 2021

Panamá, Panamá

FullStack Software Developer (Main backend)

- Backend development with .NET, MSSQL, Node.js, MongoDB, Go, and Python Flask.
- Deployments to Azure services using Docker to containerize web apps and Rest APIs.

You can check out some of my projects by going to this link: potifar.dev

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Software Engineering (dropped out third year)

Universidad Tecnológica de Panamá

• First place at the 2021 Hackathon.

REFERENCES

• Work Reference: Travis Ashcraft.

Software engineer (Game developer) - Omniscape — Transmira.

Contact: in/traviscashcraft

• Work Reference: Ricky Pan.
Worked with in several projects.

Contact: $+507\ 6457-7658$